You know I might have a death wish
But I’m always on the guest list
Real talk now I still know you’ve haven’t heard shit
But I think it’s worthless
Probably don’t deserve this
Could you please pipe down,
‘Fore I take this shot I can’t miss
Like God damn I wanna be
Just like Tiffany Day
Queuing up a track
Just to watch it replay
I wanna make ‘em all mad
That I’m rockin’ this stage
Listen to their chants
Are they screaming my name?
God damn I wanna be
Just like Tiffany Day
Queuing up a track
Just to watch it replay
I wanna make ‘em all mad
That I’m rockin’ this stage
Listen to their chants
Are they screaming my name?
I know you’ve never heard me before
But I’m the one you don’t want to ignore
Keep me in check cause I’ll open every door
I just wanted something more
I just want be adored
Like is that so bad?
Could you remind of what I have?
How do I make songs that sound like that?
Is it really enough or should I pack my bags?
Or not?
Are they screaming my name or not?
Like God damn I wanna be
Just like Tiffany Day
Queuing up a track
Just to watch it replay
I wanna make ‘em all mad
That I’m rockin’ this stage
Listen to their chants
Are they screaming my name?
God damn I wanna be
Just like Tiffany Day
Queuing up a track
Just to watch it replay
I wanna make ‘em all mad
That I’m rockin’ this stage
Listen to their chants
Are they screaming my name?